Finding Aid for Citizens for Traditional Values Records 1984-2000
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Citizens for Traditional Values Records
1984-2000
1986-1992
Citizens for Traditional Values.
The Citizens for Traditional Values record group documents four separate but interrelated organizations having many of the same members and sharing a strategy aimed at uniting conservative Christians on behalf of similarly-minded candidates for office. These organizations were The Freedom Council (1985-1987), the Michigan Committee for Freedom (1986-1992), the MCFF offshoot organization Celebrate Life (1989-1992), and the Citizens for Traditional Values (1991-present). The record group contains a variety of documentary materials such as office files, correspondence, budgets, reports, fundraising information, draft materials, and news clippings.
0369; Bt 2
6 linear feet
Bentley Historical Library University of Michigan
The materials were donated by Citizens for Traditional Values, James S. Muffett, Executive Director (donor no. 8955 ) in September 2002.
The record group is open for research.
The Freedom Council (FC -1985-1987) was an organization of devoted Christians actively working "to defend, restore and preserve religious freedom in the US." Pat Robertson, a pro-family conservative Christian, owner of the Christian Broadcasting Network and host of the 700 Club television program, founded the national organization of the Freedom Council. Local Freedom Council chapters worked to get Christians nominated and elected to state and local office, and to lobby legislators on issues of key interest. The FC also strove to fill precinct delegate positions, which would have a primary role in selecting candidates for the state legislature and for state Republican Party leadership positions. The FC was tied closely to Robertson's candidacy for president. When that faltered, the Freedom Council also folded although its overall mission to support Christian candidates and issues was continued through the Michigan Committee For Freedom (MFCC) which had many of the same membership as The Freedom Council.
The Michigan Committee For Freedom (MFCC) was founded in 1986 by David Walters, who had previously worked for the FC. The MFCC was founded to continue the values of the Freedom Council, supporting Christian candidates in state politics, particularly supplying valuable information to precinct delegate candidates on how to win elections in their areas. After the August 1986 election, over 40% of the elected Republican precinct delegates considered themselves part of the MCFF. Prospective presidential candidate Pat Robertson mirrored the values of the MCFF and had the support of many of the candidates. The MCFF and Pat Robertson's potential campaign organization were often viewed interchangeably as the two organizations had many of the same goals and supporters. In February 1987, Robertson won the Michigan Republican Presidential nomination due to the work of the MCFF delegates. Soon after the election, Americans for Robertson (1987-1988) was formed on a national level to assist Robertson with his campaign. After Robertson failed to win the national nomination, the MCFF continued their work to elect moral Christians to public office.
In 1990, the MCFF created an offshoot organization called Celebrate Life. Celebrate Life was an organization created from within the MCFF with the help of longtime staff member Maxine Elwell, dedicated to the right to life movement and the limitation or reversal of abortion legislation. The Celebrate Life had a project in three phases; the first created and printed a newspaper insert that appeared in newspapers all over Michigan. The second and third phases of the Celebrate Life project continued to seek support for the advancement of pro-life issues and advocate for support of adoption and the repeal of abortion legislation.
Since 1991, Citizens for Traditional Values (http://www.geocities.com/ctvweb/) has taken over the political activity of the MCFF. The Citizens for Traditional Values continues to promote conservative Christian political candidates for all levels of government, produces voter's guides, and lobbies for moral issues in the legislature.
The record group contains materials from The Michigan Freedom Council (MFC -1985-1987), the Michigan Committee for Freedom (MCFF -- 1986-1992), the MCFF offshoot organization Celebrate Life (1989-1992), and the Council for Traditional Values (1991-present), conservative Christian political activist groups working in Michigan. The records contains a variety of documentary materials such as office files, correspondence, budgets, reports, fundraising information, draft materials, and news clippings to give a well-rounded view of the conservative Christian political scene in Michigan.
Subjects:
Celebrate Life (Organization); Christianity and politics.; Citizens for Traditional Values.; Conservatism--Michigan--Religious aspects--Christianity.; Elections--Michigan--1988.; Evangelicalism--Michigan.; Freedom Council.; Michigan--Politics and government--1951-; Michigan--Politics and government--1981-1990.; Michigan--Politics and government--1991-2000.; Michigan Committee for Freedom.; Pro-life movement--Michigan.; Religion and politics--Michigan.; Republican Party (Mich.)
Robertson, Pat.
Subjects - Visual Material:
Citizens for Traditional Values.; Elections--United States--1988.; Robertson, Pat.
Contributors:
Michigan Committee for Freedom.; Muffett, James S.
Genre/Form:
Videotapes.; Photographs.
- Background Information
  The record group begins with a small series of Background Information (1986-1992) that includes organizational materials, brochures, and general information on the Freedom Council and the Michigan Committee for freedom. Of particular note is the oral history interview made with James Muffett describing the delegate selection process leading to the 1987 Michigan Republican presidential candidate nomination for Pat Robertson.
  - The Freedom Council, 1985-1988
    - Introduction, June 1985 (Box 1)
    - Organizational Manuals, 1985-1986 (Box 1)
    - Organizational Documents, undated (Box 1)
    - Brochure, circa 1985 (Box 1)
  - Michigan Committee For Freedom
    - Bylaws, undated (Box 1)
    - Report on permanent organization, 1986-1987 (Box 1)
    - Organizational Information, circa 1986 (Box 1)
    - Organization Lists, 1986; 1990 (Box 1)
    - Pamphlets and Information Sheets, 1986-1992; 3 folders (Box 1)
    - James Muffett, Oral History, 1989 (Box 1)
    - Statement of Purpose and Goals, circa 1991 (Box 1)
- The Freedom Council, 1985-1988
  The Freedom Council (1985-1987) series contains three subseries. The Organization subseries includes the report "Plan for Michigan" and additional organizational documents. "Involvement" includes materials on Michigan's precinct delegate nomination process as well as poll results. "Staff and Committees" consists of information on the staff and executive committee. The organization set the groundwork for the delegate selection procedures and the conservative Christian network in the state.
  - Organization
    - Plan for Michigan, 1985 (Box 1)
    - Legal restrictions on Political Activity, undated (Box 1)
    - Poll Conclusions, 1985 (Box 1)
    - Selling Memberships, undated (Box 1)
    - Michigan State Delegates, 1986-1987 (Box 1)
    - Republican Party Rules for Delegate selection, 1986-1988 (Box 1)
    - Republican Party Resolutions, undated (Box 1)
    - Robertson Follow Up Correspondence, 1985 (Box 1)
    - Americans for Robertson, 1986-1987 (Box 1)
    - Freedom Council Report by Wm. McPhail, (cassette), 1985 (Box 1)
  - Involvement
    - Training Seminar, undated (Box 1)
    - Becoming a Precinct Delegate, undated (Box 1)
    - Involvement Information, circa 1985 (Box 1)
    - Community Coordination, circa 1985 (Box 1)
    - Soliciting Members for the Pennsylvania Freedom Council, 1985 (Box 1)
    - Memos, 1985-1986 (Box 1)
    - Video Script, 1985-1986 (Box 1)
  - Staff and Committees
    - Michigan Staff, National Office Staff, 1985 (Box 1)
    - Correspondence, 1985-1987 (Box 1)
    - Personnel Packet, undated (Box 1)
    - Report on Financial Obligations for Employees, undated (Box 1)
    - Finance Director, 1985 (Box 1)
    - Executive Committee Responsibilities, undated (Box 1)
    - Executive Board and Staff Lists, undated (Box 1)
    - Executive Board Meeting, 1985-1986 (Box 1)
    - Executive Board Minutes, 1985-1986 (Box 1)
    - Personnel Files (includes James Muffett, John and Michelle Miller, Bob Baldwin), 1985-1986 (Box 1)
- Michigan Committee For Freedom, 1986-1992
  Michigan Committee for Freedom (1986-1992) contains ten subseries. "Organizational Files" (1986-1992) include materials on the organization, its structure, goals, mission, and history. The "Board of Directors Files" (1986-1992) consist of membership lists, meeting minutes, reports, and budgets. "Correspondence" (1986-1991) contains both ingoing and outgoing messages. Correspondence from John and Michelle Miller give some detail about the transition from MFC to MCFF. "Fundraising" (1985-1991) consists of donor correspondence, donor information, and fundraising events. "Financial Records" (1986-1991) include budgets, spreadsheets, and reports. "Chapter Records" (1987-1990) include materials from the district organizations of the MCFF.
  The "Convention and Delegates" (1985-1990) subseries consists of rules and procedures for convention attendance, convention strategy files, delegate recruitment and training, the delegate election process, write-in campaigns, polls and results of elections. The materials describe the part delegate selection plays in the Michigan Republican Party and strategies used when electing delegates. The "Voters Guide" materials (1990-1992) include candidate questionnaires, press releases, and distribution information. "Visual Materials" (ca. 1988) consists of videos by Marlene Elwell and Pat Robertson on behalf of the campaign of Pat Robertson. The "News Clippings" (1987-1989) subseries contains clippings from Michigan newspapers about the Michigan Republican delegate process, Pat Robertson's election, and the MCFF role in the win.
  - Organizational Files, 1986-1992
    - Memos and Clippings, 1985-1986 (Box 1)
    - Clippings and Fact Sheets, 1986 (Box 1)
    - Organizing the Michigan Republican Party, undated (Box 1)
    - Victory Communications International: Operation Michigan, 1986 (Box 1)
    - Parliamentary Procedure, 1986 (Box 1)
    - Event Scheduling Handbook, 1987 (Box 1)
    - Committee for Informed Citizens, 1988 (Box 1)
    - Restructuring, 1988 (Box 1)
    - Leadership Seminar Invitations, 1989 (Box 1)
    - Notebook of Information, 1990 (Box 1)
    - Freedom Focus Newsletter, 1988-1989 (Box 1)
  - MCFF Board of Directors Files, 1986-1992
    - Members, 1986; 1988; 1992 (Box 1)
    - Meetings (Minutes, Reports, Budgets), 1987-1989; 5 folders (Box 1)
    - Meetings (Minutes, Reports, Budgets), 1990-1991; 3 folders (Box 2)
    - State Delegate Totals by County, undated (Box 2)
  - Correspondence, 1986-1991
    - General, 1986-1987; 2 folders (Box 2)
    - Expansion of Political Action Committees, 1987 (Box 2)
    - Training Materials, 1986-1987 (Box 2)
    - Miller, John and Michelle (includes transition information from Freedom Council), 1987 (Box 2)
    - County/City Leaders, 1988 (Box 2)
    - Example Correspondence for Donors, 1988-1989 (Box 2)
    - Correspondence with Memos, October 1988-March 1989 (Box 2)
    - Sent, 1988-1990 (Box 2)
    - Mailings, 1990 (Box 2)
    - General, 1991; 3 folders (Box 2)
    - Regarding Newsletter Drafts, 1991; 2 folders (Box 2)
    - Form Letters, undated (Box 2)
  - Fundraising, 1985-1991
    - Donor Correspondence
      - Donor Packet, 1986 (Box 2)
      - Fundraising Ideas, 1987 (Box 2)
      - Event Planning Checklist, 1987 (Box 2)
      - Fundraising Assistance to Pat Robertson (donor list), 1987-1988 (Box 2)
      - Major donor mailing, 1988 (Box 2)
      - Potential donor mailing, 1988 (Box 2)
      - Friend-raising, 1988 (Box 2)
      - Eagle Club Membership, 1989 (Box 2)
      - Fundraising Ideas, undated (Box 2)
      - Donor List, 1990 (Box 2)
      - Fundraising, 1991 (Box 2)
      - For Your Information Materials, 1991 (Box 2)
    - Donor Information
      - Beale, Robert, 1987 (Box 2)
      - Boeckmann, Herbert F. II, and Jane, 1988 (Box 2)
      - Ellingwood Meeting (financial documents), 1987 (Box 2)
      - Gandolfo, Joe M., 1987 (Box 2)
      - Huston, Jim, 1987 (Box 2)
      - Middendorf, Isabelle, 1987 (Box 2)
      - Williams, Arthur L. Jr., 1987 (Box 2)
    - Fundraising Events
      - Pat Robertson visits, 1985; 1986; 1987 (Box 2)
      - Christmas Fundraiser, 1988 (Box 2)
      - Rally, April 2-3, 1990 (Box 2)
      - Oliver North event (includes photographs), 1990 (Box 2)
      - John Stormer Event, 1990-1991 (Box 2)
      - Posthumous Fundraiser, 1991 (Box 2)
      - Politics and Family Luncheon, 1991 (Box 2)
      - Oakland County Fundraiser, 1991 (Box 2)
      - Lansing Fundraiser, 1991 (Box 2)
  - Financial Records, 1986-1991
    (See also Board of Directors Files for additional Financial Information)
    - Balance Sheet and Income/ Expenses, 1986 (Box 3)
    - Spreadsheets, 1986 (Box 3)
    - Budget, 1986 (Box 3)
    - Report, Year's End, 1986 (Box 3)
    - Expenditures, 1986-1987 (Box 3)
    - Richard McLellan (lawyer) Correspondence, 1986-1988 (Box 3)
    - Reports and proposals, 1989-1990; 2 folders (Box 3)
    - Weekly Reports, 1991 (Box 3)
  - MCFF Chapters, 1987-1990
    - General, 1987-1988 (Box 3)
    - 6th District, Oakland County Conservative Republican Mailing List, 1987-1988 (Box 3)
    - 15th District, Washtenaw County, 1988 (Box 3)
    - 16th District, 1987-1988 (Box 3)
    - Kent County Correspondence, 1988 (Box 3)
    - Leadership Questionnaires Returned, 1990 (Box 3)
    - Precinct Plan Leader's Handbook, undated (Box 3)
  - Convention and Delegate Files, 1985-1990
    - Strategy and Results
      - Involvement Strategy, undated (Box 3)
      - Memos to David Walters, 1985 (Box 3)
      - Intern / Consultant Search, circa 1986 (Box 3)
      - Pre-Convention Strategy, 1986 (Box 3)
      - State Convention Manual, 1986 (Box 3)
      - State Convention, 1986 (Box 3)
      - Republican Committee Meetings, 1986; 2 folders (Box 3)
      - Delegate Training, 1986 (Box 3)
      - Precinct Delegates, 1986 (Box 3)
      - Delegate Seminar, 1986-1987 (Box 3)
      - Pre-Convention (County / District) Seminar, 1986-1987 (Box 3)
      - Pre-Convention Strategy, 1987 (Box 3)
      - Convention Strategy, circa 1987 (Box 3)
      - County Conventions, 1987 (Box 3)
      - Convention Information and Planning, 1987 (Box 3)
      - State Convention, 1987 (Box 3)
      - GO-PAC (Get Organized Political Action Committee) manual, circa 1988 (Box 3)
      - GO-PAC, 1988 (Box 3)
      - Memos to District Leaders, 1988 (Box 3)
      - James Muffett Campaign for Precinct Delegate, 1988 (Box 3)
      - Campaign Flyers Blanks, circa 1988 (Box 3)
      - Michigan Convention Chronicle, 1988 (Box 3)
      - State Republican Convention, January 1988 (Box 3)
      - State Convention Coordinator's Packet, September 1988 (Box 3)
      - State Convention, 1988 (Box 3)
      - State Convention, February 1989 (Box 3)
      - Election Training for Precinct Delegates, undated (Box 3)
      - Delegate Recruitment, 1990 (Box 3)
      - Delegate Information, 1990 (Box 3)
    - Training Files
      - Convention Rules and Strategy (County, State), 1986 (Box 3)
      - "Any 86" Conventions, 1986 (Box 3)
      - State Convention, 1986 (Box 3)
      - State Delegates, 1986 (Box 3)
      - Delegate Files by County A-G, 1986 (Box 3)
      - District Reports, 1986-1987 (Box 4)
        include Allegan, Berrien, Cass, Grand Traverse, Houghton, Kent, Lapeer, Lake, Leelanu, Manistee, Mason, Macomb, Montcalm, Muskegon, Newaygo, Ottawa, St. Joseph, and Van Buren counties
      - District Totals with notes (presidential Candidates), 1986-1987 (Box 4)
      - Training Seminar, 1987 (Box 4)
      - State Convention, 1987 (Box 4)
      - Nominating Petition, 1988 (Box 4)
      - Delegate Filings, 1990 (Box 4)
      - Write-In Delegate Campaign, 1990 (Box 4)
      - Data Processing for Precinct Races, 1990 (Box 4)
      - Post Election Briefing, 1990 (Box 4)
      - Ingham County Delegates, 1990 (Box 4)
    - Delegates, 1985-1987
      - Republican State Committee, 1985 (Box 4)
      - Republican Party Year End Report, 1985 (Box 4)
      - Gallup Poll for CBN, 1985 (Box 4)
      - Republican Convention Dates, 1986 (Box 4)
      - Call to Conventions, 1986; 2 folders (Box 4)
      - Republican Party By-Laws, 1986 (Box 4)
      - Action 86 (Right to Life Political Action Committee), 1986 (Box 4)
      - County Conventions, 1986 (Box 4)
      - Republican Convention, 1986 (Box 4)
      - Republican Delegates for State Central Committee, Write in Delegate Information, 1986 (Box 4)
      - Precinct Delegates, 1986 (Box 4)
      - Delegate Information, 1986-1987; 2 folders (Box 4)
      - District / State Convention, 1987 (Box 4)
      - Pat Robertson at Freedom Rally, 1987 (Box 4)
      - Memo to Pat Robertson, 1987 (Box 4)
      - Walters Notes, 1987 (Box 4)
      - Memos from David Walters, 1987-1988 (Box 4)
      - Republican Delegate Selection and Instruction, 1987-1988 (Box 4)
      - Republican Convention, County and Congressional Districts Information and Rules, 1988 (Box 4)
      - Rules for Delegate and Alternate Selection, County Conventions, 1988 (Box 4)
      - Precinct Delegates, 1988 (Box 4)
      - Republican Convention Report, 1988 (Box 4)
      - Convention Candidate Focus, 1989 (Box 4)
      - Candidate Research Questionnaire, 1989 (Box 4)
      - Republican Convention Delegate Survey by Calvin College, 1989 (Box 4)
    - Candidate Information, 1985-1990
      - Baldwin, Bob, 1988 (Box 4)
      - Cropsey, Alan, 1989-1990 (Box 4)
      - Durant, Clark, 1989-1990; 3 folders (Box 4)
      - Goschka, Mike, 1987; 1990 (Box 4)
      - Kemp, Jack, 1985-1986 (Box 4)
      - Schuette, Bill, 1990 (Box 4)
  - Visual, circa 1988
    - Marlene Elwell Video #2, Robertson for President speech, circa 1988 (Box 5)
    - Pat Robertson, "Iowa Caucus Training Video", circa 1988 (Box 5)
    - Americans For Pat Robertson Video Volunteer, "A New Vision For America", circa 1988 (Box 5)
  - Voters Guides, 1990-1992
    - Voters Guide Information, 1989-1992
      - Voters Registration Committee, 1989-1990 (Box 5)
      - Printed Voter's Guides, 1990 (Box 5)
      - Ingham County Republicans, 1990-1991 (Box 5)
      - Voter's Guide Notebook, circa 1990 (Box 5)
      - Voter's Guide Celebrate Life Notebook, circa 1990 (Box 5)
      - Post-Election Analysis, 1990 (Box 5)
    - Voters Guide 1, 1990
      - Memos (Box 5)
      - Candidate Responses (Box 5)
      - General (Box 5)
      - Biblical Scoreboard Flyer (Box 5)
      - Donors (Box 5)
      - Leadership Mailing (Box 5)
    - Voters Guide 2, 1990
      - Quotes (Positive) (Box 5)
      - Correspondence (Negative) (Box 5)
      - Distributor's Packet (Box 5)
      - Press Releases (Box 5)
      - Candidate Questionnaires / Mailings (Box 5)
      - Return Candidates Questionnaires (Box 5)
      - Questionnaires Printed in Voter's Guide (Box 5)
      - Press Packet (Box 5)
      - Targeting (Box 5)
      - Primary Winners (Box 5)
      - Dick Rolfe (candidate follow-up) (Box 5)
      - Presidential Scoreboard (Box 5)
    - Voter Information, 1992
      - State Convention Candidate Information, August 1992 (Box 5)
      - Impact 92 Strategic Plan, 1992 (Box 5)
      - Proposal "A" (Plan to end tax funded abortion in Michigan), 1992 (Box 5)
      - Republican Party of Michigan Rules for Delegates, 1992 (Box 5)
      - State Convention, 1992 (Box 5)
  - News Clippings
    - Michigan Clippings and Notes, 1987; 7 folders (Box 5)
    - Michigan Clippings, 1988-1989; 2 folders (Box 5)
- Celebrate Life, 1989-1992
  Celebrate Life (1989-1992) contains materials from the Celebrate Life Organization, divided into six subseries. "Background" (1989-1990) includes correspondence and a certificate of assumed name so MCFF could work under the name of Celebrate Life. "Team 1000" (1989-1990) was the volunteer team who helped fundraise and coordinate the Celebrate Life project. "Phase I" (1989-1990) included the creation of newspaper inserts distributed across the state promoting a pro-life viewpoint. "Phase II" (1989-1990) includes fundraising correspondence, cooperation with other area groups, and a Rally held in 1990. "Research" (1989-1990) includes research on aspects of abortion and abortion issues used to support the project. "Phase III" (1990-1991) materials consist of fundraising correspondence, news releases, and budgets.
  - Background
    - Welcome letter, circa 1989 (Box 6)
    - Pat Robertson support correspondence, 1989 (Box 6)
    - Correspondence, 1989-1990 (Box 6)
    - Project Description, 1990
      - Beginning Budget, 1990 (Box 6)
      - Phase I and II Budgets/ Charts, 1990 (Box 6)
      - Master Copies of Correspondence, 1989-1990 (Box 6)
    - Certificate of Assumed Name for MCFF, Celebrate Life, 1990 (Box 6)
  - Team 1000
    - Job Descriptions, undated (Box 6)
    - Updates, 1989 (Box 6)
    - General, 1990 (Box 6)
    - Team List, 1990 (Box 6)
    - Meeting Notes, 1990 (Box 6)
    - Pastor Packet, Recruiting, 1990 (Box 6)
    - Buck Back Proposal, circa 1990 (Box 6)
  - Phase I
    - Press Release, 1990 (Box 6)
    - Newspaper Insert, 1990
      - Draft, 1989-1990 (Box 6)
      - Research, 1989-1990 (Box 6)
      - Advertisement Information, 1990 (Box 6)
    - Responses to Newspaper Insert
      - Pro-Choice, 1990 (Box 6)
      - Pro-Life (with donation forms), 1990 (Box 6)
      - Original Responses
        - Pro-Life, 1990 (Box 6)
        - Good Pro-Life Comments, 1990 (Box 6)
        - Good Pro-Choice Comments, 1990 (Box 6)
        - Pro-Choice, 1990 (Box 6)
    - Press Packet, 1990 (Box 6)
    - Celebrate Life Signers, Written Pieces for Ad Campaign, 1990 (Box 6)
    - Donor Correspondence, 1990 (Box 6)
    - Report, circa 1990 (Box 6)
    - Video Script and Research, 1990 (Box 6)
  - Phase II
    - Reports (Box 6)
    - Materials, 1990 (Box 6)
    - Contacts, 1990 (Box 6)
    - Correspondence, 1990 (Box 6)
    - Notes and Telephone Calls for Michigan Regions, 1990 (Box 6)
    - Rally Information and Flyers, 1990 (Box 6)
    - Notes, 1990 (Box 6)
    - Cooperative Organizations, 1990 (Box 6)
    - Pro-Life Testimonies, undated (Box 6)
    - Honorary Board Correspondence, undated (Box 6)
    - Celebrate Life Groups and Contacts, 1990 (Box 6)
    - Fundraising Lists, 1990 (Box 6)
  - Abortion Research, 1988-1990
    - Clippings
      - Civil Disobedience: Operation Rescue, 1988-1989 (Box 6)
      - Medical Aspects, undated (Box 6)
      - Tax Funding, 1989-1990 (Box 6)
      - General, 1990 (Box 6)
      - Ultrasound Video, Shan Richard, 1989 (Box 6)
      - Right to Life Lifespan, 1989-1990 (Box 6)
    - Phase III, 1990-1991
      - Example Correspondence, 1990 (Box 6)
      - Second Annual Ad Campaign, 1991 (Box 6)
      - Budget / Activities, 1991 (Box 6)
- Citizens for Traditional Values, 1987-1992; 1998-2000
  Citizens for Traditional Values is a small series containing donor and supporter correspondence, and news clippings about the organization in the early 1990's. Newsletters and brochures include information about the organization after 1998.
  - Quotable Correspondence, 1987-1991 (Box 6)
  - News clippings, 1988-1991 (Box 6)
  - Donor Correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 6)
  - Freedom Club Correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 6)
  - Impact 92, Plan for State Convention, 1992 (Box 6)
  - Newsletters and Brochures, 1998-2000 (Box 6)